blogymate.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy : BlogyMate.com

BlogyMate can take your personal information very carefully. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use the website available at BlogyMate.com.

**Website Visitors**

BlogyMate collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. BlogyMate’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how BlogyMate’s visitors use its Website. From time to time, BlogyMate may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Website. 

BlogyMate also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. BlogyMate does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Collection of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to the Website choose to interact with BlogyMate in ways that require BlogyMate to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that BlogyMate gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. BlogyMate does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

BlogyMate does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you believe that a child has provided BlogyMate with personally identifiable information without the consent of his or her parent or guardian, please contact us at [support@blogymate.com](mailto:support@blogymate.com) . If BlogyMate becomes aware that a child under age 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information.

**Statistics**

BlogyMate may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to the Website. For instance, BlogyMate may monitor the most popular blogs on the BlogyMate.com site to help identify spam. BlogyMate may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, BlogyMate does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

**Security of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

BlogyMate discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on BlogyMate’s behalf or to provide services available at the Website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if BlogyMate or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that BlogyMate goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of BlogyMate may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, BlogyMate will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. 

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations or as described above, BlogyMate discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when BlogyMate believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BlogyMate, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the BlogyMate Website and have supplied your email address, BlogyMate may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with BlogyMate and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. BlogyMate takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

You should also be aware that if you submit information to “chat rooms,” “forums” or “message boards” such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.   
For users outside the United States, please note that any personally-identifiable information you enter into the Website will be transferred out of your country and into the United States. You consent to such transfer through your use of the Website. You also warrant that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country and into the United States. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by BlogyMate. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BlogyMate does not own or control, or employees that BlogyMate does not manage. The Website contains links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and BlogyMate and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

**Protection**

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Selection/Opt-out**

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no further notices.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. BlogyMate uses cookies to help BlogyMate identify and track visitors, their usage of the BlogyMate Website, and their Website access preferences. BlogyMate visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the BlogyMate Website, with the drawback that certain features of BlogyMate’s Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

**Address Book Data**

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives BlogyMate access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BlogyMate may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in BlogyMate’s sole discretion. If we do then we’ll notify you by posting the amended policy on the Website or by emailing you of the nature of the modifications along with a link to the modified document so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. 

You will have the opportunity to correct, update, modify or delete this information by sending an e-mail to [support@blogymate.com](mailto:support@blogymate.com) . Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.
